Board of Trustees Records, 1877-[ongoing]
Smith College Archives
Board of Trustees Records
1877-[ongoing]
Smith College. Board of Trustees.
RG 30
2 boxes (.9 linear ft.)
14 boxes (15.2 linear ft.)
Smith College Archives Northampton, MA
The Board of Trustees records contain materials describing the function, duties, and organization of the Smith College Board of Trustees, including the by-laws, as well as information on various Board members throughout college history.
Historical Note
The Board of Trustees governs many aspects of the college, including financial decisions. Members include the President of the College, the President of the Alumnae Association, the head of student government, alumnae trustees elected by the Alumnae Association, and other regular members elected by the Board of Trustees.
Harriet (Bliss) Ford graduated from Smith College in 1899. She served as the first chairman of the Alumnae Fund Committee and as a director of the Alumnae Association before becoming a trustee of the college in 1928. She was the first resident trustee, and lived at the college from 1931 until the end of her term in 1936. Harriet Ford also participated in national service organizations, such as the American Red Cross and YWCA, was chairman of the Paris committee of the Smith College Relief Unit in France, and was a civic leader in the city of Northampton until her death in 1964.
Dorothy Nepper Marshall graduated from Smith College in 1935, and went on to receive her PhD from Bryn Mawr College. She was a dean at Bryn Mawr for more than twenty years, before moving to work for UMass Boston. She held the position of vice-chancellor there for several years, and was considered to be one of the highest-ranking women in education. She held many trusteeships, including the Ford Foundation, Holy Cross College, and Smith College. She was trustee of Smith from 1959-1969, and then again as Chairman from 1975 until her retirement in 1980.
Charlotte (Cheever) Tucker graduated from Smith College in 1891. She was a trustee of the college from 1889-1895.
Scope and Contents of the Collection
The Board of Trustees records contain materials describing the function, duties, and organization of the Smith College Board of Trustees, including the by-laws, as well as information on various members throughout college history. The collection contains records of such activities as building construction, college planning, committees, promotion and tenure, and the election of a new president. The collection includes an alphabetical listing of trustees, as well as more detailed information on several individuals. Types of materials include extensive correspondences, such as letters and memos, newsletters, pamphlets, lists of trustees, by-laws, and newspaper articles.
The Harriet (Bliss) Ford individual files contain materials describing her activities as a trustee of the college, member of the Alumnae Association, and civic leader. The materials cover the tour of the country she made as a trustee speaking to prospective students and alumnae clubs. Types of materials include extensive correspondences, publications, articles, and poetry by Harriet Ford, photographs, newspaper articles, and speeches.
The Dorothy Nepper Marshall individual files contain materials from her years as a scholar, consisting almost entirely of correspondences with institutions, as well as some biographical information. Types of materials include letters, memos, newspaper clippings, photographs, some writings, notes, and research materials.
The Charlotte (Cheever) Tucker files contain materials describing her daily life, some family history, and some of her activities with the Alumnae Association and as a trustee of the college. Types of materials include correspondences, journals, genealogy charts, tuition bills, photographs, and writings.
Organization of the Collection:
The Board of Trustees records are organized into four series:
Series I: Meetings and Minutes
Series II: Correspondence
Series II: Committee on Tenure and Promotion
Series IV: Individual Trustee Biographical Files
Information on Use
Terms of Access and Use
The records are open for research according to the regulations of the Smith College Archives.
Access to boxes #268 and #275.3 is restricted.
History of the Collection
The Board of Trustees Records were donated over a period of time to the Smith College Archives from a variety of sources.
Additional Information
Related Material
Researchers should also view:
30. Harriet Bliss Ford Papers
30. Dorothy Nepper Marshall Papers
30. Charlotte Cheever Tucker Papers
32. Office of the President Records
- Meetings-Notices of 1871-1874, 1926 (Box 268, Folder 1)
- Minutes-Discredited 1888-, 1918, 1916 (Box 268, Folder 2)
- Minutes 1920-1928 (Box 268, Folder 3)
- John M. Greene Award-Euphemia Hare Steffey, '44 1992 (Box 268, Folder 4)
- John M. Greene Award Citations 1980-1998 (Box 268, Folder 5)
- John M. Greene Committee 1985-1990 (Box 268, Folder 6)
- General (Box 269, Folder 1)
- General (Box 269, Folder 2)
- Alumnae Trustees 1888 (Box 269, Folder 3)
- By-Laws 1925-1999 (Box 269, Folder 4)
- List Trustees 1968-1976 (Box 269, Folder 5)
- Correspondence
  - Appointment of a new President 1917, 1956 (Box 269, Folder 6)
  - Dormitory Construction 1917 (Box 269, Folder 7)
  - Honorary Degrees 1916-1917 (Box 269, Folder 8)
  - Infirmary 1917 (Box 269, Folder 9)
  - Clark L. Seelye to John M. Greene 1894-1905 (Box 269, Folder 10)
  - Sabbatical Leaves 1917 (Box 269, Folder 11)
- Meetings and Minutes (Box 269, Folder 12)
- Neilson Chair 1930-1936 (Box 269, Folder 13)
- Photographs 1933-1964 (Box 269, Folder 14)
- Planning Committee 1956-1957 (Box 269, Folder 15)
- Pledges to General Education Board 1921 (Box 269, Folder 16)
- Allen, Charles H. (Box 269, Folder 17)
- Baldwin, Ruth (Bowles) 1887 (Box 269, Folder 18)
- Baldwin, William H. 1896 (Box 269, Folder 19)
- Ballou, Emily (Crabbe) 1919 (Box 269, Folder 20)
- Brooks, Harvey (Box 269, Folder 21)
- Buck, Paul Herman 1952-1962 (Box 269, Folder 22)
- Clark, Charles N. 1895-1911 (Box 269, Folder 23)
- Cone, Kate (Morris) 1879 (Box 269, Folder 24)
- Dawes, Anna L.
  - Dawes, Anna L. 1889-1938 (Box 269, Folder 25)
  - Dawes, Anna L.-Correspondence 1889-1896 (Box 269, Folder 26)
  - Dawes, Anna L.-Correspondence to Charlotte (Cheever) Tucker 1890-1894 (Box 269, Folder 27)
- Day, Pomeroy 1951-1960 (Box 269, Folder 28)
- DeConingh, Edward H. 1963 (Box 269, Folder 29)
- Emerson, Kendall 1917-1935 (Box 269, Folder 30)
- Fosdick, Harry Emerson-Recording (Box 269, Folder 31)
- Fosdick, Harry Emerson 1925-1969 (Box 269, Folder 32)
- Committee on Promotion and Tenure
  - Correspondence
    - General 1920-1923 (Box 270, Folder 1)
    - General 1923 (Box 270, Folder 2)
    - General 1924 (Box 270, Folder 3)
    - General 1925, undated (Box 270, Folder 4)
    - William Allan Neilson and Mary Van Kleeck 1923-1925 (Box 270, Folder 5)
- Ford, Harriet (Bliss)
  - General 1899-1935, undated (Box 271, Folder 1)
  - Biographical Record 1922-1964 (Box 271, Folder 2)
  - Capen House 1935 (Box 271, Folder 3)
  - Century of Progress 1933-1934 (Box 271, Folder 4)
  - European Recovery Plan 1948 (Box 271, Folder 5)
  - Fight for Freedom 1941-1942 (Box 271, Folder 6)
  - Five and Seven Colleges 1932-1933 (Box 271, Folder 7)
  - Ford, George Burdett 1919-1941 (Box 271, Folder 8)
  - French Relief 1945-1946 (Box 271, Folder 9)
  - League of Women Voters 1952 (Box 271, Folder 10)
  - Mss- Pearman, Mabel capelle undated (Box 271, Folder 11)
  - Mss- Summering on Tyler Court undated (Box 271, Folder 12)
  - Neilson, William Allan
    - Chair of Research 1935 (Box 271, Folder 13)
    - Death-Resolution of Alumnae Association 1946 (Box 271, Folder 14)
    - Dinners 1929 (Box 271, Folder 15)
    - Dinners 1937 (Box 271, Folder 16)
    - Portraits 1929 (Box 271, Folder 17)
    - Scholarships 1932-1933 (Box 271, Folder 18)
    - Speech 1937 (Box 271, Folder 19)
  - New Creation 1930 (Box 271, Folder 20)
  - Photographs 1877-1892 (Box 271, Folder 21)
  - Photographs 1892-1896 (Box 271, Folder 22)
  - Photographs 1897-1900 (Box 271, Folder 23)
  - Photographs 1901-1919 (Box 271, Folder 24)
  - Photographs 1920- (Box 271, Folder 25)
  - Photographs-Birthday Party 1956 (Box 271, Folder 26)
  - Photographs-Index (Box 271, Folder 27)
  - Publications
    - "the Cricket" 1904 (Box 272, Folder 1)
    - "In the Smith Tradition" 1945 (Box 272, Folder 2)
    - League of Nations 1925 (Box 272, Folder 3)
    - "March-Time Duet" 1935 (Box 272, Folder 4)
    - "The Minor Poet" undated (Box 272, Folder 5)
    - "A House for the Towne" 1952-1954 (Box 272, Folder 6)
    - Poetry Scrapbook 1897-1928 (Box 272, Folder 7)
    - "Return of a Native" 1899-1932 (Box 272, Folder 8)
    - "Smith College Weekly" Editorial 1933 (Box 272, Folder 9)
    - "Stephen Phillips" 1903 (Box 272, Folder 10)
    - "The Tel Club" undated (Box 272, Folder 11)
    - "The Trustees Look at the Future" 1932 (Box 272, Folder 12)
  - The Reel 1933-1934 (Box 272, Folder 13)
  - The Reel 1875-1953 (Box 272, Folder 14)
  - Resignation 1936-1955 (Box 272, Folder 15)
  - Smith Clubs 1932 (Box 272, Folder 16)
  - Smith Primer 1946 (Box 272, Folder 17)
  - 75th Anniversary Correspondence 1949-1950 (Box 272, Folder 18)
  - Snow, Florence H.-Retirement Skit 1948 (Box 272, Folder 19)
  - Trustee Appointment 1931 (Box 272, Folder 20)
  - Trustees, Criticism-Barnes, H.E. 1928-1934 (Box 272, Folder 21)
  - Trustees, Criticism-Parshley, H. 1934 (Box 272, Folder 22)
  - Trustees-Meetings 1931 (Box 272, Folder 23)
  - Trustees-Reports undated (Box 272, Folder 24)
  - United Nations Weekend 1948-1949 (Box 272, Folder 25)
  - War Bond Campaign 1942-1944 (Box 272, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence
    - Alumnae Association 1936-1937 (Box 273, Folder 1)
    - Anderson, Dorothy May 1936 (Box 273, Folder 2)
    - Baldwin, Ruth (Bowles) 1932 (Box 273, Folder 3)
    - Bacon, Josephine Daskam 1921 (Box 273, Folder 4)
    - Berliss, Ruth Ernestine 1932 (Box 273, Folder 5)
    - Bolster, Susanne Ricker 1934 (Box 273, Folder 6)
    - Chase, Mary Ellen 1935 (Box 273, Folder 7)
    - Churchill, Ruth (Pierson) 1949-1950 (Box 273, Folder 8)
    - Comstock, Ada Louise 1931 (Box 273, Folder 9)
    - Conkling, Grace (Hazard) 1924 (Box 273, Folder 10)
    - Cutter, Annie Spencer 1935 (Box 273, Folder 11)
    - Davidson, Adaline (Allen) 1933 (Box 273, Folder 12)
    - Davies, Hallie Flanagan 1952 (Box 273, Folder 13)
    - Development Fund 1962 (Box 273, Folder 14)
    - Eller, Alice (Seely) 1935 (Box 273, Folder 15)
    - Evans, Bess Orr 1935 (Box 273, Folder 16)
    - Emerson, Kendall 1932 (Box 273, Folder 17)
    - Finley, John Huston 1935 (Box 273, Folder 18)
    - Ford, Harriet (Bliss) 1936 (Box 273, Folder 19)
    - Gleason, Emily (Clapp) 1936 (Box 273, Folder 20)
    - Hill, Edith Naomi undated (Box 273, Folder 21)
    - Hodgkinson, Laura (Cabot) 1952 (Box 273, Folder 22)
    - Kimball, Charlotte (Smith) undated (Box 273, Folder 23)
    - League of Women Voters 1932 (Box 273, Folder 24)
    - Martin, Caro (Taylor) 1931 (Box 273, Folder 25)
    - Morrow, Elizabeth (Cutter) 1933-1934 (Box 273, Folder 26)
    - Murphy, Mary Carolyn 1934 (Box 273, Folder 27)
    - Neilson, William Allan-Faculty Salaries 1927 (Box 273, Folder 28)
    - Neilson, William Allan 1929-1935 (Box 273, Folder 29)
    - Norton, Katherine (Garrison) undated (Box 273, Folder 30)
    - Perkins, James H. 1932 (Box 273, Folder 31)
    - Prince, Winifred (Notman) 1925 (Box 273, Folder 32)
    - Rausch, Louise (Cornell) 1932 (Box 273, Folder 33)
    - Ripperger, Henrietta (Sperry) 1932 (Box 273, Folder 34)
    - Sabin, Florence Rena 1935 (Box 273, Folder 35)
    - Spahr, Jean (Fine) 1928 (Box 273, Folder 36)
    - Teagle, Alice (Wright) 1933-1935 (Box 273, Folder 37)
    - Wells, Marguerite Milton undated (Box 273, Folder 38)
    - Right, Benjamin Fletcher 1950-1956 (Box 273, Folder 39)
    - Zinsser, Dorothy (Douglas) 1935 (Box 273, Folder 40)
  - Speeches
    - General Speeches (Box 274, Folder 1)
    - Anniversary 1925 (Box 274, Folder 2)
    - Alumnae Council 1926 (Box 274, Folder 3)
    - Alumnae Association 1927 (Box 274, Folder 4)
    - Alumnae Association 1928 (Box 274, Folder 5)
    - Alumnae Association 1929 (Box 274, Folder 6)
    - Alumnae Association 1932 (Box 274, Folder 7)
    - Alumnae Association 1935 (Box 274, Folder 8)
    - Alumnae Association 1936 (Box 274, Folder 9)
    - Alumnae Council 1932 (Box 274, Folder 10)
    - Alumnae Council 1935 (Box 274, Folder 11)
    - Alumnae Council 1936 (Box 274, Folder 12)
    - Baldwin Round House Table (Box 274, Folder 13)
    - Bennett School, Buffalo, New York 1935 (Box 274, Folder 14)
    - Bridgeport, Conn. 1935 (Box 274, Folder 15)
    - Burnham School 1952 (Box 274, Folder 16)
    - Class of 1899 1899-1909 (Box 274, Folder 17)
    - Class of 1924 1924 (Box 274, Folder 18)
    - Class of 1927 1927 (Box 274, Folder 19)
    - Growth in Opportunities for College Women in the professions and covations (Box 274, Folder 20)
    - M.I.T. Student Visitors (Box 274, Folder 21)
    - Press Board (Box 274, Folder 22)
    - Smith Clubs 1934 (Box 274, Folder 23)
    - Smith in Washington 1934-1935 (Box 274, Folder 24)
    - Student Assembly 1932 (Box 274, Folder 25)
    - Student Assembly 1934 (Box 274, Folder 26)
    - Student Assembly 1935 (Box 274, Folder 27)
    - Student Assembly 1936 (Box 274, Folder 28)
    - Student Assembly 1946 (Box 274, Folder 29)
  - Tours
    - Tour 1 1933 (Box 275, Folder 1)
    - Tour 1-Alumnae Association 1933 (Box 275, Folder 2)
    - Tour 1-Dallas 1933 (Box 275, Folder 3)
    - Tour 1-Denver 1933 (Box 275, Folder 4)
    - Tour 1-Kansas City 1933 (Box 275, Folder 5)
    - Tour 1-Omaha 1933 (Box 275, Folder 6)
    - Tour 1-St. Louis 1933 (Box 275, Folder 7)
    - Tour 1-Tulsa 1933-1934 (Box 275, Folder 8)
    - Tour 2 1934 (Box 275, Folder 9)
    - Tour 2-Atlanta 1934 (Box 275, Folder 10)
    - Tour 2-Augusta, Charlotte, Charleston, Richmond 1934 (Box 275, Folder 11)
    - Tour 2-Wilmington 1935 (Box 275, Folder 12)
    - Tour 2-Winston-Salem 1932-1934 (Box 275, Folder 13)
    - Tour 3 1934 (Box 275, Folder 14)
    - Tour 3-Duluth 1934-1935 (Box 275, Folder 15)
    - Tour 3-Milwaukee 1934 (Box 275, Folder 16)
    - Tour 3-Minneapolis and Oshkosh 1934 (Box 275, Folder 17)
    - Tour 3-St. Paul (Box 275, Folder 18)
    - Tour 3-South Bend 1934 (Box 275, Folder 19)
    - Tour 4 1936 (Box 275, Folder 20)
    - Tour 5 1935-1936 (Box 275, Folder 21)
    - Tour 5-Albuquerque 1936 (Box 275, Folder 22)
    - Tour 5-Alumnae Association 1936 (Box 275, Folder 23)
    - Tour 5-California 1936 (Box 275, Folder 24)
    - Tour 5-Santa Fe 1936 (Box 275, Folder 25)
    - Tour 5-Washington 1936 (Box 275, Folder 26)
- Marshall, Dorothy Nepper
  - Biography 1946-1986 (Box 275.1, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence
    - General 1946-1975 (Box 275.1, Folder 2)
    - General 1976-1985, undated (Box 275.1, Folder 3)
    - Bryn Mawr 1970-1985, undated (Box 275.1, Folder 4)
    - College of the Holy Cross 1970-1980 (Box 275.1, Folder 5)
    - Ford Foundation 1972-1985, undated (Box 275.1, Folder 6)
    - National Endowment for the Humanities 1974-1982 (Box 275.1, Folder 7)
    - Northfield Mt. Herman 1981-1985, undated (Box 275.1, Folder 8)
    - UMass Boston 1971-1981, undated (Box 275.1, Folder 9)
    - Smith College 1959-1982 (Box 275.1, Folder 10)
    - University of Southern Maine 1980-1985 (Box 275.2, Folder 1)
  - Writings/Notes 1937-1976 (Box 275.2, Folder 2)
  - Writings/Notes 1977-1985 (Box 275.2, Folder 3)
  - Writings/Notes undated (Box 275.2, Folder 4)
  - Writings/Notes-University of Southern Maine 1983-1985 (Box 275.2, Folder 5)
  - Research File 1982-1985, undated (Box 275.2, Folder 6)
  - Photographs 1970-1982, undated (Box 275.2, Folder 7)
  - Memorabilia 1972-1981, undated (Box 275.2, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence-Bryn Mawr 1969-1985, undated (Box 275.3, Folder 1)
    RESTRICTED
  - Correspondence-Smith Board of Trustees 1972-1985 (Box 275.3, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence-Smith Consultancy 1980 (Box 275.3, Folder 3)
  - Galbraith, Archibald 1929-1939 (Box 276, Folder 1)
  - Gillett, Arthur L. 1923 (Box 276, Folder 2)
  - Gillett, Edward Bates 1899, undated (Box 276, Folder 3)
  - Greene, John Morton 1883 (Box 276, Folder 4)
  - Gulliver, Charlotte Chester 1884 (Box 276, Folder 5)
  - Hanes, John W. 1942 (Box 276, Folder 6)
  - Henderson, Alexander I. 1951-1954 (Box 276, Folder 7)
  - Hidden, Molly 1951 (Box 276, Folder 8)
  - Hofer, Philip 1936, 1984 (Box 276, Folder 9)
  - Hood, Donald 1999 (Box 276, Folder 10)
  - Hoskins, Harold Boies 1941-1951 (Box 276, Folder 11)
  - Hubbard, George W. 1876 (Box 276, Folder 12)
  - Ingersall, Robert S. 1966 (Box 276, Folder 13)
  - Kane, Amanda (Bryan) 1927 (Box 276, Folder 14)
  - Knight, Francis McMaster 1946-1956 (Box 276, Folder 15)
  - LaCroix, Morris Felton 1935-1955 (Box 276, Folder 16)
  - Lamont, Thomas S. 1941 (Box 276, Folder 17)
  - Lamont, Thomas William, Jr. 1928-1976 (Box 276, Folder 18)
  - Lewis, Phoebe Reese 1989 (Box 276, Folder 19)
  - McCallum, George Bliss 1918-1928 (Box 276, Folder 20)
  - Mendenhall, Thomas C. 1959-1975 (Box 276, Folder 21)
  - Michel, Anthony L. (Box 276, Folder 22)
  - Morgan, Constance Morrow 1933-1995 (Box 276, Folder 23)
  - Noyes, Lucia (Clapp) 1881 (Box 276, Folder 24)
  - Morgenthau, Robert M. 1977 (Box 276, Folder 25)
  - Northrup, Birdsey Grant (Box 276, Folder 26)
  - Park, Edward A. 1872-1892 (Box 276, Folder 27)
  - Parker, Franklin Eddy Jr. 1949 (Box 276, Folder 28)
  - Perkins, James Handasyd 1935 (Box 276, Folder 29)
  - Raymond, Eleanor Agnes 1919-1981 (Box 276, Folder 30)
  - Rosenberry, Cicely 1962 (Box 276, Folder 31)
  - Sachs, Paul J. 1965 (Box 276, Folder 32)
  - Seelye, Julius H. 1849-1914 (Box 276, Folder 33)
  - Seelye, L. Clark to Charlotte (Cheever) Tucker 1893-1896 (Box 276, Folder 34)
  - Seelye, L. Clark to Anna L. Dawes 1890-1893 (Box 276, Folder 35)
  - Sheffield, Frederick 1967 (Box 276, Folder 36)
  - Smith, Frank (Box 276, Folder 37)
  - Stevenson, George Stanley 1921-1931, 1932-1949 (Box 276, Folder 38)
  - Symonds, H. Gardiner 1950-1954 (Box 276, Folder 39)
  - Taylor, Nell Cochrane 1951 (Box 276, Folder 40)
  - Tyler, William Seymour 1871-1946 (Box 276, Folder 41)
  - Tyler, William Seymour-Photographs 1897 (Box 276, Folder 42)
  - Tucker, Charlotte (Cheever) (Box 276, Folder 43)
  - Valentine, Alan Chester 1933 (Box 276, Folder 44)
  - Van Dusen, Henry P. 1945-1950 (Box 276, Folder 45)
  - Vaughan, Richard Henry 1971-1980 (Box 276, Folder 46)
  - Wallace, Rodney 1885-1947 (Box 276, Folder 47)
  - Washburn, H. Bradford 1938, 1967 (Box 276, Folder 48)
  - Washburn, William Barrett 1850-1980 (Box 276, Folder 49)
  - White, Alexander M. 1956-1960 (Box 276, Folder 50)
  - Woods, Robert McEwen 1893-1924 (Box 276, Folder 51)
  - Wyzanski, Judge Charles Edward Jr. 1949-1952 (Box 276, Folder 52)
- Tucker, Charlotte (Cheever)
  - Biography 1858-1917, undated (Box 277, Folder 1)
  - Biography-Genealogy 1901-1931, undated (Box 277, Folder 2)
  - Biography-Misc. Lists, Account Book 1878-1928, undated (Box 277, Folder 3)
  - Biography-Journals 1882-1888, 1894, 1903 (Box 277, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence (Box 277, Folder 5)
  - Education 1877-1879 (Box 277, Folder 6)
  - Lecture Notes-First Chapel 1877 (Box 277, Folder 7)
  - Lecture Notes-Old Testament Lectures by Pres. Seelye 1878 (Box 277, Folder 8)
  - Poetry, Speech, Report 1871-1916 (Box 277, Folder 9)
  - Photographs 1867-1910 (Box 277, Folder 10)
  - Journal 1879 (Box 277, Folder 11)
  - Journal 1879-1880 (Box 277, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence
    - General 1880-1927, undated (Box 278, Folder 1)
    - Burton, Marion LeRoy 1910 (Box 278, Folder 2)
    - Caverno, Julia Harwood 1895 (Box 278, Folder 3)
    - Cheever, Charlotte Barrell to family 1878-1885 (Box 278, Folder 4)
    - Cheever, Louisa Sewall 1917 (Box 278, Folder 5)
    - Frost, Mary Adeline 1896 (Box 278, Folder 6)
    - Harris, George 1920 (Box 278, Folder 7)
    - Howells, William Dean 1923 (Box 278, Folder 8)
    - Huntington, Eliza Prentiss 1917-1931 (Box 278, Folder 9)
    - Jordan, Mary Augusta 1891 (Box 278, Folder 10)
    - Kapp, Marie F. 1893 (Box 278, Folder 11)
    - Rockwood, Ellen (Cheever) 1886-1927 (Box 278, Folder 12)
    - Scudder, Vida Dutton 1893 (Box 278, Folder 13)
    - Seelye, Laurenus Clark 1909 (Box 278, Folder 14)
    - Tucker, Charlotte to William J. Tucker 1901-1926 (Box 278, Folder 15)
    - Tucker, William Jewett 1886-1887 (Box 278, Folder 16)
    - Tucker, William Jewett 1887 (Box 278, Folder 17)
    - Tucker, William Jewett 1887 (Box 278, Folder 18)
    - Tucker, William Jewett 1901 (Box 278, Folder 19)
    - Wheeler, Elizabeth (Cheever) 1919-1925 (Box 278, Folder 20)
    - Woods, Robert Archey 1925 (Box 278, Folder 21)